textmarks.com 2019-01-02

# TextMarks SMS Service, Mass Text Messaging | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how TextMarks, Inc. and its affiliated companies (“ ** _TextMarks_** ”, “ ** _our_** ”, “ ** _us_** ”, and “ ** _we_** ”) collect, use, and disclose information about you. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our website, messaging platform, any mobile application we may offer, and other online products and services (collectively, the “ ** _Services_** ”) or when you otherwise interact with us. 

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you a notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy before you use or submit any information on or through the TextMarks Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, use, disclosure and sharing of your information as further outlined below in this Privacy Policy. 

### Collection of Information

#### Information You Provide to Us

We collect information you provide directly to us in the course of using the Services, including personally identifiable information. For example, we collect information when you create an account, set up automatic bill pay, participate in any interactive features of the Services, fill out a form, participate in a contest or promotion, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, phone number(s), email address, postal address, credit card or other billing information and any other information you choose to provide. We may use third-party payment processors to bill you through a payment account linked to your TextMarks account for use of the paid Services. The processing of payments will be subject to the terms, conditions, and privacy policies of the payment processor in addition to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. 

#### Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including: 

  * **Usage Information:** We collect log information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.
  * **Device Information:** We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information.
  * **Location Information:** We may collect precise information about the location of your mobile device, but only with your express consent. Once you have consented to the collection of such precise location information via your mobile device, you may adjust this consent by managing your Location Services preferences through the settings of your mobile device. For more details, please see "Your Choices" below.
  * **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:** We use various technologies to collect information, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see "Your Choices" below.

#### Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including but not limited to reseller programs, referral programs, identity verification services, credit bureaus, mailing list providers and publicly available sources. 

### Use of Information

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to: 

  * Provide, maintain and improve our Services;
  * Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and invoices;
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
  * Communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events offered by TextMarks and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with the Services;
  * Detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of TextMarks and others;
  * Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests;
  * Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions and to process entries and deliver rewards;
  * Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
  * Carry out any other purpose described to you at the time the information was collected.

### Sharing of Information

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy: 

  * With vendors, consultants, third party payment processors and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of TextMarks or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company;
  * Between and among TextMarks and our current and future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and other companies under common control and ownership; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.
  * We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

### Data Retention

The time periods for which we retain your personal information will depend on the purposes for which we use it. We will retain your personal information for so long as is necessary to provide the Services, unless applicable law requires we either dispose of it or keep it longer. We may also continue to store your personal information to allow us to resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, comply with legal obligations and/or for other legally permissible purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

### Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others

We may allow others to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and in applications. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites and applications, including your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by TextMarks and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on the Services and other websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](https://www.aboutads.info/choices). 

### Security

TextMarks takes reasonable measures designed to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. 

### Transfer of Information to the U.S. and Other Countries

TextMarks is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing, transfer and storage of information in and to the U.S. and other countries, where you may not have the same rights and protections as you do under local law. 

### Your Choices

#### Account Information

You may update, correct or delete information about you at any time by logging into your online account or emailing us at **tmsupport@textmarks.com**. If you wish to delete or deactivate your account, please contact us at **tmsupport@textmarks.com** , but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time. 

#### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Removing or rejecting browser cookies does not necessarily affect third party flash cookies used in connection with the Services. To delete or disable flash cookies please visit <http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html> for more information. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Services. 

#### Promotional Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails or text messages from TextMarks by following the instructions in those emails or text messages. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations. 

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at **tmsupport@textmarks.com**. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: **tmsupport@textmarks.com**
